å 

* | Articles

* | Links

* * *

Close

* * *

Privacy Policy
==============

* * *

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which \[Your Website Name\] collects, uses, maintains, and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of \[Your Website URL\] (“Website”). This privacy policy applies to the Website and all products and services offered by \[Your Website Name\]. Information Collection Personal Identification Information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including but not limited to when Users visit our Website, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features, or resources we make available on our Website. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, and other personally identifiable information. Users may, however, visit our Website anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Website-related activities. Non-personal Identification Information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Website. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer, and technical information about Users’ means of connection to our Website, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized, and other similar information. Web Browser Cookies

Our Website may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. Users’ web browsers place cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Website may not function properly. How We Use Collected Information

\[Your Website Name\] may collect and use Users’ personal information for the following purposes:

    To personalize user experience: We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Website.
    To improve our Website: We continually strive to improve our Website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
    To send periodic emails: We may use the email address to respond to inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

How We Protect Your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage, and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information, and data stored on our Website. Sharing Your Personal Information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates, and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. Third-Party Websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Website that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors, and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Website. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites that have a link to our Website, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies. Changes to This Privacy Policy

\[Your Website Name\] has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this Website, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Website. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this Website, please contact us at \[your contact email\].

* * *

#### See also:

Toggle

Code

This website uses cookies. By continuing to read, you accept the use of cookies. Accept

Article Progress Tracker
